const level12questions = [
    
  
  {
    question: "14 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["42", "9", "3", "187"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["36", "83", "124", "91"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["98", "210", "168", "4"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["141", "7", "87", "196"],
    answer: "7"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["190", "96", "178", "125"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["128", "51", "211", "150"],
    answer: "150"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["36", "79", "84", "66"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["99", "178", "105", "74"],
    answer: "105"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["80", "173", "122", "112"],
    answer: "112"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["70", "124", "93", "30"],
    answer: "70"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["8", "36", "28", "117"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["157", "153", "190", "18"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["86", "216", "114", "70"],
    answer: "70"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["130", "105", "121", "173"],
    answer: "130"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["101", "162", "56", "42"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["15", "24", "45", "217"],
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["72", "13", "134", "32"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["22", "130", "188", "48"],
    answer: "22"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["179", "108", "45", "110"],
    answer: "110"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["57", "75", "45", "2"],
    answer: "45"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["113", "182", "147", "16"],
    answer: "182"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["128", "181", "2", "47"],
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["98", "158", "80", "88"],
    answer: "88"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["101", "189", "39", "107"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["90", "75", "18", "171"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  
  {
    question: "5 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["60", "45", "136", "37"],
    answer: "45"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["74", "12", "120", "82"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["107", "5", "80", "76"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["1", "208", "59", "224"],
    answer: "1"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["75", "41", "81", "90"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["202", "12", "175", "125"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["12", "134", "154", "51"],
    answer: "154"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["77", "141", "135", "82"],
    answer: "135"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["34", "114", "32", "48"],
    answer: "32"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["20", "105", "122", "13"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["33", "119", "171", "20"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["10", "96", "39", "70"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["12", "214", "17", "169"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["100", "26", "95", "206"],
    answer: "26"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["207", "165", "34", "35"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["56", "45", "74", "173"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["72", "116", "195", "137"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["111", "1", "10", "214"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["14", "106", "153", "117"],
    answer: "117"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["19", "174", "14", "54"],
    answer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["60", "132", "176", "123"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["72", "35", "184", "124"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["80", "105", "165", "25"],
    answer: "105"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["225", "41", "216", "49"],
    answer: "225"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["19", "11", "213", "46"],
    answer: "11"
  },
  
  {
    question: "6 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["30", "186", "36", "1"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["116", "80", "28", "51"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["207", "200", "143", "91"],
    answer: "143"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["168", "218", "15", "201"],
    answer: "168"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["93", "157", "12", "206"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["11", "89", "77", "108"],
    answer: "77"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["140", "7", "105", "33"],
    answer: "33"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["180", "142", "93", "147"],
    answer: "180"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["15", "27", "81", "161"],
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["140", "44", "133", "191"],
    answer: "140"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["56", "161", "219", "63"],
    answer: "63"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["45", "82", "165", "220"],
    answer: "165"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["174", "77", "44", "73"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["112", "221", "139", "205"],
    answer: "112"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["24", "104", "9", "105"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["120", "143", "200", "169"],
    answer: "143"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["51", "167", "14", "156"],
    answer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["33", "25", "57", "86"],
    answer: "25"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["30", "169", "180", "181"],
    answer: "180"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["106", "117", "27", "137"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["212", "75", "149", "11"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["70", "194", "99", "78"],
    answer: "99"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["5", "182", "108", "146"],
    answer: "182"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["68", "40", "55", "119"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["120", "104", "78", "86"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  
  {
    question: "13 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["129", "176", "169", "134"],
    answer: "169"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["82", "77", "210", "5"],
    answer: "210"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["150", "15", "194", "58"],
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["98", "173", "22", "71"],
    answer: "98"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["143", "116", "216", "135"],
    answer: "135"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["78", "22", "3", "117"],
    answer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["176", "213", "30", "207"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["88", "154", "132", "63"],
    answer: "132"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["45", "192", "215", "206"],
    answer: "45"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["132", "120", "53", "159"],
    answer: "120"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["120", "78", "84", "33"],
    answer: "78"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["135", "154", "40", "8"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["24", "37", "139", "111"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["51", "38", "161", "56"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["182", "162", "21", "120"],
    answer: "120"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["108", "24", "169", "15"],
    answer: "108"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["14", "198", "129", "19"],
    answer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["70", "139", "154", "169"],
    answer: "154"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["80", "102", "130", "197"],
    answer: "130"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["139", "213", "138", "84"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["142", "43", "93", "5"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["217", "170", "103", "90"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["132", "203", "172", "170"],
    answer: "132"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["150", "157", "99", "7"],
    answer: "7"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["122", "151", "23", "90"],
    answer: "90"
  },
  
  {
    question: "12 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["149", "156", "51", "104"],
    answer: "156"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["202", "79", "20", "151"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["33", "66", "131", "79"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["70", "113", "134", "157"],
    answer: "70"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["16", "111", "48", "132"],
    answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["91", "172", "158", "187"],
    answer: "91"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["98", "78", "217", "72"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["120", "48", "69", "44"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["214", "24", "172", "216"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["82", "50", "154", "60"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["50", "52", "17", "2"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["39", "29", "126", "120"],
    answer: "120"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["39", "174", "10", "44"],
    answer: "44"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["1", "82", "44", "66"],
    answer: "66"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["105", "42", "202", "172"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["195", "23", "56", "52"],
    answer: "52"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["88", "120", "150", "71"],
    answer: "88"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["32", "158", "6", "104"],
    answer: "104"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["61", "47", "65", "33"],
    answer: "65"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["7", "154", "108", "118"],
    answer: "108"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["33", "41", "39", "6"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["36", "99", "50", "45"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["212", "220", "168", "70"],
    answer: "70"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["24", "16", "198", "139"],
    answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["163", "159", "36", "60"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  
  {
    question: "6 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["35", "155", "6", "88"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["36", "18", "189", "127"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["101", "198", "40", "66"],
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["9", "141", "60", "28"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["223", "200", "43", "144"],
    answer: "144"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["106", "130", "165", "100"],
    answer: "100"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["81", "219", "176", "77"],
    answer: "77"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["146", "42", "54", "171"],
    answer: "54"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["72", "135", "183", "196"],
    answer: "196"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["31", "88", "56", "214"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["56", "6", "25", "8"],
    answer: "56"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["139", "36", "1", "175"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["179", "190", "18", "77"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["33", "13", "126", "163"],
    answer: "13"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["65", "102", "110", "28"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["173", "49", "12", "113"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["96", "47", "225", "44"],
    answer: "96"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["21", "72", "126", "61"],
    answer: "21"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["148", "208", "40", "79"],
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["20", "102", "195", "165"],
    answer: "195"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["92", "3", "168", "65"],
    answer: "65"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["97", "10", "55", "148"],
    answer: "55"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["1", "30", "86", "88"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["210", "144", "27", "47"],
    answer: "210"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["125", "42", "80", "146"],
    answer: "42"
  },
  
  {
    question: "2 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["33", "24", "177", "62"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["37", "80", "21", "221"],
    answer: "21"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["154", "176", "124", "30"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["116", "190", "99", "9"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["105", "178", "100", "81"],
    answer: "81"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["165", "10", "203", "16"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["223", "4", "175", "13"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["201", "116", "16", "27"],
    answer: "16"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["54", "43", "86", "78"],
    answer: "54"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["104", "76", "96", "62"],
    answer: "104"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["225", "119", "60", "110"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["25", "48", "221", "155"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["53", "112", "127", "40"],
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["70", "60", "53", "61"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["123", "181", "7", "156"],
    answer: "156"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["146", "3", "30", "23"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["108", "207", "49", "216"],
    answer: "49"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["142", "107", "78", "63"],
    answer: "63"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["12", "119", "100", "217"],
    answer: "12"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["181", "68", "13", "43"],
    answer: "13"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["56", "84", "8", "165"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["63", "10", "24", "214"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["10", "130", "59", "16"],
    answer: "10"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["62", "2", "159", "145"],
    answer: "2"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["188", "117", "145", "166"],
    answer: "117"
  },
  
  {
    question: "2 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["4", "120", "67", "123"],
    answer: "4"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["168", "77", "26", "98"],
    answer: "168"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["208", "120", "171", "50"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["151", "196", "28", "175"],
    answer: "28"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["128", "97", "19", "33"],
    answer: "33"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["134", "11", "95", "80"],
    answer: "11"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["75", "3", "171", "94"],
    answer: "75"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["170", "50", "84", "94"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["47", "40", "86", "76"],
    answer: "40"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["130", "80", "6", "22"],
    answer: "22"
  },
  {
    question: "5 x 7 = ?",
    options: ["109", "35", "184", "33"],
    answer: "35"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["116", "148", "110", "70"],
    answer: "110"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 13 = ?",
    options: ["196", "42", "174", "195"],
    answer: "195"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["18", "34", "57", "194"],
    answer: "18"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["45", "15", "5", "156"],
    answer: "5"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["40", "55", "14", "210"],
    answer: "14"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["16", "21", "62", "36"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 9 = ?",
    options: ["126", "68", "189", "2"],
    answer: "126"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["205", "212", "190", "99"],
    answer: "99"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["148", "61", "26", "58"],
    answer: "26"
  },
  {
    question: "11 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["53", "43", "121", "62"],
    answer: "121"
  },
  {
    question: "14 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["84", "188", "82", "107"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["24", "209", "145", "221"],
    answer: "24"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 12 = ?",
    options: ["165", "145", "170", "72"],
    answer: "72"
  },
  {
    question: "3 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["26", "9", "16", "66"],
    answer: "9"
  },
  
  {
    question: "9 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["62", "93", "201", "36"],
    answer: "36"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 5 = ?",
    options: ["132", "50", "105", "154"],
    answer: "50"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["198", "84", "128", "134"],
    answer: "84"
  },
  {
    question: "7 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["52", "183", "9", "98"],
    answer: "98"
  },
  {
    question: "13 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["128", "39", "97", "129"],
    answer: "39"
  },
  {
    question: "6 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["25", "120", "48", "108"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["9", "19", "6", "62"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["132", "64", "20", "105"],
    answer: "64"
  },
  {
    question: "12 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["182", "137", "42", "48"],
    answer: "48"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 4 = ?",
    options: ["170", "109", "8", "6"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["83", "112", "140", "216"],
    answer: "140"
  },
  {
    question: "2 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["194", "20", "33", "154"],
    answer: "20"
  },
  {
    question: "8 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["155", "77", "106", "120"],
    answer: "120"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 6 = ?",
    options: ["68", "75", "6", "32"],
    answer: "6"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 14 = ?",
    options: ["35", "126", "214", "53"],
    answer: "126"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 1 = ?",
    options: ["213", "15", "175", "169"],
    answer: "15"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 15 = ?",
    options: ["1", "89", "73", "60"],
    answer: "60"
  },
  {
    question: "9 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["26", "68", "27", "96"],
    answer: "27"
  },
  {
    question: "10 x 8 = ?",
    options: ["80", "183", "139", "102"],
    answer: "80"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 11 = ?",
    options: ["165", "73", "148", "11"],
    answer: "165"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["147", "170", "30", "212"],
    answer: "30"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 10 = ?",
    options: ["150", "62", "7", "126"],
    answer: "150"
  },
  {
    question: "4 x 2 = ?",
    options: ["30", "8", "128", "34"],
    answer: "8"
  },
  {
    question: "1 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["3", "19", "212", "169"],
    answer: "3"
  },
  {
    question: "15 x 3 = ?",
    options: ["45", "91", "215", "146"],
    answer: "45"
  },
];

export default level12questions;